<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on SAFE ADVICE</title>
    <link>https://sygqy.com/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on SAFE ADVICE</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 03:59:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://sygqy.com/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://sygqy.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 04:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sygqy.com/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to our site, if you have any issues, please contact us by sending us an email at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:allsupportvisit@gmail.com&#34;&gt;allsupportvisit@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDPR Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://sygqy.com/pages/gdpr-privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 04:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sygqy.com/pages/gdpr-privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At Our Site, accessible at sygqy.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Our Site and how we use it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:allsupportvisits@gmail.com&#34;&gt;allsupportvisits@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr&#34;&gt;General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are a Data Controller of your information.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://sygqy.com/pages/privacy-policy-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 16:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sygqy.com/pages/privacy-policy-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last updated: September 25, 2024&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy has been created with the help of the Privacy Policy Generator.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>https://sygqy.com/pages/terms-and-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 16:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sygqy.com/pages/terms-and-conditions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last updated: September 25, 2024&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please read these terms and conditions carefully before using Our Service.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;interpretation-and-definitions&#34;&gt;Interpretation and Definitions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;interpretation&#34;&gt;Interpretation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;definitions&#34;&gt;Definitions&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the purposes of these Terms and Conditions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Affiliate&lt;/strong&gt; means an entity that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with a party, where “control” means ownership of 50% or more of the shares, equity interest or other securities entitled to vote for election of directors or other managing authority.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Country&lt;/strong&gt; refers to: Florida, United States&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Company&lt;/strong&gt; (referred to as either “the Company”, “We”, “Us” or “Our” in this Agreement) refers to Our Site.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Device&lt;/strong&gt; means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cellphone or a digital tablet.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service&lt;/strong&gt; refers to the Website.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Terms and Conditions&lt;/strong&gt; (also referred as “Terms”) mean these Terms and Conditions that form the entire agreement between You and the Company regarding the use of the Service. This Terms and Conditions agreement has been created with the help of the Terms and Conditions Generator.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third-party Social Media Service&lt;/strong&gt; means any services or content (including data, information, products or services) provided by a third-party that may be displayed, included or made available by the Service.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Website&lt;/strong&gt; refers to Our Site, accessible from &lt;a href=&#34;https://sygqy.com&#34;&gt;https://sygqy.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You&lt;/strong&gt; means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;acknowledgment&#34;&gt;Acknowledgment&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These are the Terms and Conditions governing the use of this Service and the agreement that operates between You and the Company. These Terms and Conditions set out the rights and obligations of all users regarding the use of the Service.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
